How sleazy. I want some kimchi.
Muhyeok! Muhyeok!
Muhyeok! Get up!
Muhyeok!
[Episode 2]
[Choi Yun's Concert
- Special Offline Meetup]
Is Choi Yun's stylist coordinator in here?
Excuse me, aren't you Choi Yun's coordinator?
- Yes. Me?
- Choi Yun is done singing.
Okay.
This lady right next to me...
Everyone knows who she is, right?
Yes!
She has always been my idol...
She is my rival who I can never beat.
She is the one who always makes me happy.
My mother.
Everyone remembers my mom
as one of the greatest movie stars,
but her dream has always been
to become a singer, like me.
When I was stressed and exhausted,
she always sang me a certain song
with my head upon her lap.
Today, I would like to share that song with everyone.
Muhyeok!
Muhyeok! Don't leave me like this!
Wake up!
Muhyeok!
Don't leave me!
I'm afraid two stray bullets are lodged in his skull.
We removed the bullet lodged
in the left brain hemisphere,
but the one in the afterbrain, I'm afraid it was just
too risky for us to operate on that one.
The risk of him dying from surgery was way too high,
so we had to leave it there.
It was miracle enough that he escaped death,
but we can't be sure how long he'll be able to live.
When he wakes up, he may experience changes
in character and personality
because his left brain has been damaged.
He may feel nervous at times or even become violent.
What kind of person was he before?
No, Muhyeok. No!
They said you need rest.
You're not normal.
There's still a bullet in your head.
Didn't the doctor tell you?
Muhyeok!
You're back, right?
I knew you'd be back.
I knew you would.
Go to Korea.
I got you a ticket, packed some clothes,
and enough money to last you a lifetime.
Leave. Your flight's tonight.
If you go home, you'll die.
Jason is trying to kill you.
Jason was the one who sent that car.
He probably burned your house down.
I'm sorry, Muhyeok. This is all I have to give.
You saved our lives,
but I'm so sorry this is all I have to give.
If he wants me dead, I guess I'll just die.
If you want to die, die in Korea.
Don't die here like a dog, go back and end it there.
Am I dying?
We'll soon be landing in Incheon International Airport.
We hope you make beautiful memories in Seoul,
the city of hope and love. Thank you.
Poison.
You took this and died, didn't you?
Oh, careless love!
Why didn't you leave me a single drop?
Oh, dagger...
Let my heart be its sheath.
Take me, death!
Take me to Romeo.
Let's make you into a movie star.
You might win an Academy Award.
When did you get here? You said it'd take 40 minutes.
I think it's time you made your debut.
Let's go to the studio. I'll be your manager.
A customer came to buy a laundry machine
and took the catalogue.
Stop fooling around and do your job!
I'm leaving.
How long will your waste
your life as Yun's coordinator?
I think you have the potential to be great.
I'm not saying that just because you're my sister.
You wouldn't be as good as Kang Min, but you...
I know myself better than you. Mind your own business.
You know how hard it was for me to
get you this position, right?
Better not get fired again.
Yes?
Yun?
Okay. I'll be there soon.
What did Yun do now?
You poor thing. You can't ever catch a break!
I got to go! See you later!
Okay, go. Go. Go.
I did something bad, too...
They told me today was my last day...
My dumb boss...
Wow. He's hot.
If he had money too, I'd marry him in a heartbeat!
Wow, he's so good looking.
Cha Muhyeok. Is it true that you were adopted?
[Danny Anderson (Cha Muhyeok, 27)]
Yup.
You must have few memories
of your mother and of Korea.
I don' 'member nothing.
Please pardon Muhyeok.
He's good at Korean,
but he hasn't learned proper Korean.
I hope no one takes offense.
Yes, let's bring Cha Muhyeok on stage. Please come up.
Cha Muhyeok. Please come here.
Please join us up here.
Tell us something that might help us find your family.
Do you have anything that was given
to you before you were adopted?
We're airing live right now.
This show is live.
Excuse me, Cha Muhyeok...
This must be a necklace with a story.
So is this what you had when you were adopted?
Yup.
When and how did you get it?
I dunno.
Can you please hold it up to the camera?
That necklace is pretty.
Where did I see that?
It doesn't seem like a necklace from Korea.
Can you get out and ask the lady
where she got that necklace?
Hello?
Can you go ask?
Yes, yes, ma'am.
Is that platinum or silver?
It's quite unique.
It's got ring with a string tied to it.
Time to put on some pants...
It says, "Together."
It's written in Korean. It seems very important.
Hey! Change it back!
We have to keep watching so we can find your family.
No! I want to watch cartoons!
Wait a second. Let me just watch a minute of it.
No!
Mom!
I'm going to watch cartoons!
["Forever"]
Turn it back to the cartoons, Kim Galchi!
Eunchae!
Yun!
He read this, and disappeared
in the middle of rehearsal.
What are we going to do?
I'll find him.
Here's a napkin.
No. I'm going to ask my mom
to clean it when I meet her.
"A woman is..."
"Is... Is..."
["That time of the month!"
Clean women's pads! Feels great!]
"Is long."
"To a woman... It is..."
"P... Pad."
You're super dumb.
How can you not know how to read that?
Oh, my!
How dare you hit my kid!
What a strange man. Are you okay?
Oh, a pad...
Pad.
"Feels..."
"Feels great."
I love you.
You know you're the only one I love, right?
Cut! Okay! Next scene.
What the heck is that? Go check it out.
We're in the middle of filming! Can you keep it down?
Come on! Please!
Are you crazy?
Hey! Don't you see we're filming?
Sorry!
I'll take care of it.
Just go. Leave it to me.
I'm sorry!
Yun!
It's me! Open the door!
Yun, please don't do this.
Please! Please don't do this.
What are you going to do if reporters see this?
I don't get it. I seriously don't understand that girl.
I'm going nuts!
I'm gonna die!
Am I your servant?
"Am I your servant?"
Do you want to die?
"Do you want to die?"
Studio?
Director?
Yeah.
Where?
Cha Muhyeok.
Nice to meet you. Let's go.
That doesn't taste good.
No, I want to drink this.
Mom, you ordered that one. I ordered the cola.
No, I ordered the cola. Give me it.
That little boy called us after watching the show.
He told us that his mother has
the same exact same necklace.
- Give it!
- No!
- It's mine!
- Give it! Mine!
Give it! It's mine!
No! I want it!
Give it! I want the cola!
Mine! I want it!
No, I was drinking it!
Give it!
[Together Forever]
She's like this because she was
in a car accident a long time ago.
At age seven, a grandpa told me
she got hit by a truck in front
of the orphanage and hurt her head.
Read it.
Read what's written in your ring.
Don't know.
I don't know.
Can't your mother read?
Is your mom an illiterate retard?
She's not retarded.
If she can't read at her age, how is she not retarded?
It's because she hasn't learned all of her letters yet.
She can read up to the seventh letter.
What does it say?
Forever.
Forever?
You can't read, either?
There are some words I can, and some words I can't.
But I'm not stupid.
Compared to your mom, I'm 1,000 times smarter!
"Forever... Together..."
Do you know me?
Who are you?
I'm Seo-kyeong.
Yun Seo-kyeong.
Eunchae, let's go home and make some spicy rice cakes.
Okay.
I'll forget her.
Minju. From now on,
I'll completely erase her from my mind.
Without leaving a single trace.
I'm going to completely delete her.
Goodbye, Kang Minju.
It's goodbye forever!
- Yun.
- What?
Don't lie.
Grab a taxi and go home.
I want to talk to Minju alone.
I want to talk her alone. Go home.
You have cab fare, right?
Yes.
I'm going to go get drunk. Will you wait here?
I'll take a shot, come back,
and do something about Minju.
I'll tell her not to make you sad.
I'll knock some sense into her.
Or I'll break her legs so that
she can't meet anyone else.
Yeah. She's got it coming!
Wait a second, I'll be back.
Don't lay a finger on her.
It's not Minju's fault.
She warned me.
I'm the crazy one.
Yun!
Kang Minju!
I'll wait.
- Get rid of him, and come to me.
- Hey!
Or you don't have to get rid of him.
I'll do it for you.
You probably have to wait along time.
I started to date him just a week ago.
I can wait. A month is enough right?
Choi Yun. You bastard!
Hey!
You're dead! Dead!
How dare you hit him!
Eunchae!
Oh, god!
Let me see. Did you break something?
Geez...
Are you okay to walk?
"Forever. Together."
Look at the state your face is in
at your age.
Can't you wait at least till it heals?
I'm all right. It doesn't hurt.
Say you're all right one more time
and I'm leaving you on the streets!
I'm telling you I'm fine because I'm fine
and that it doesn't hurt because it doesn't.
"All right"? "Doesn't hurt"?
Are you made of steel? Are you a robot?
Why would you get involved?
Are you the 911 rescue squad?
I'm really fine.
Get out.
Fine, it hurts.
It hurts so much, I think I'll die. I'm not fine.
I'll never be all right. Not even after I die.
Now, I feel bad.
I want to die.
What am I going to do with you?
I found the orphanage where
you and Yun Seo-kyeong were from.
You two were twins.
Twins?
You two had the necklaces when you were
discovered in front of the orphanage.
That's all I know.
Seaweed rolls!
- Delicious seaweed rolls!
- One, please!
Yes, sir!
Here you go!
Thank you!
Seaweed rolls for sale!
Seaweed rolls! Seaweed rolls for sale!
Don't skip breakfast! Have some seaweed rolls!
Seaweed rolls for sale!
Don't skip breakfast!
Have some seaweed rolls!
We have seaweed rolls!
Sir, seaweed rolls for sale!
Seaweed rolls for sale!
Don't skip breakfast! Have some seaweed rolls!
How much is it, kid?
Two dollars.
- Give me two.
- Yes, sir.
Mine's only a dollar.
- Really? Get me two, then.
- Sure.
Why do you always cheat?
What do you mean cheat?
You always cheat. Why do you take my customers?
Your customer is my customer. They're not the same.
If they buy yours, they're yours.
If they buy mine, they're mine.
That's not right!
How dare you! Disrespectful little brat!
That's right. Rude brat.
You little...
How much is all this?
Is that enough?
Buy these, buy these.
I'll give them to you at half price.
Why is your mom sleeping like that?
She was making seaweed rolls all night.
I'll give you all these for 300 dollars.
I mean 200 dollars.
- Ma'am?
- Yes, sir?
You cheated earlier, didn't you?
Pardon?
You cheated.
No. I didn't cheat.
If you admit you cheated, I'll buy everything here.
Okay, I did. I cheated.
If you ever cheat him again, I won't let it slide.
Wake up, guys!
The sun is high in the sky!
Samchae!
Wake up!
Eunchae!
Sukchae! Wake up!
Samchae!
Get up!
I thought it was too quiet these days.
How did you get a black eye?
I fell while I was walking.
It'll be fine in a couple days.
You're not Yun's coordinator,
you're his bodyguard, right?
Is Samchae awake?
She's in the room.
Mom, shh!
- Shouldn't you get going?
- I'm going.
You...
Why are you wearing sunglasses indoors?
It's personal preference, Dad.
Did you get plastic surgery?
No way!
Hurry and come out.
I have to take the madam to the studio.
Madam my butt.
After I earn a lot of money, I'm moving out
of this house just to avoid hearing about her.
I'm going to the store with your dad. Peel some onions.
Maybe I'm pregnant. I can't stand the smell of onions.
Are there people coming to Yun's house?
Yun's mother is. She's getting ready for a photoshoot.
She's putting on a show for her famous son.
How arrogant.
Don't say that.
Mom, did you get botox again?
Okay... Mom, the camera is rolling.
Don't be nervous. Okay! One, two...
A cup of coffee with my son.
The simple joys of life.
No! Let me do it again.
I don't like the shade of my lipstick.
Why? It's pretty.
A cup of coffee with my son.
The simple joys of life.
I'll be showing you my precious son.
Hello, I'm Choi Yun.
I heard my mom was doing a self camera,
so... I'm just cutting in a little.
Mom, can I say something to you?
What? Say it. Say it...
Mother, go over there and sit.
What? Why?
Okay. That's it.
You see. When I think about my mother,
I'm so grateful it brings tears to my eyes.
She brought me into this world, raised me so perfectly,
always gave me so much love.
Mom, you are my sunshine.
My world. You know that, right?
I love you, Mom.
I love you.
You have to be more respectful to your elders, Mister.
That lady's had a sad life, too.
Later on, tell her that you're sorry.
Say that you're sorry, okay?
No.
Mister, are you a gangster?
Yes.
What is your name?
Galchi. Like the fish you eat.
- That's your name?
- Yes.
What grade are you in?
I don't go to school.
Even though I don't go to school, I can read.
And I speak a little English. I'm pretty smart.
- What about your father?
- I don't have one.
Hey, Grandpa!
Oh, hey. Let's have barbecue pork!
This is the man I told you about. From that show.
Who has the necklace. Who's from Australia.
Got the same eyes as your mother's.
You grew up well.
Have you ever had barbecue pork, Korean style?
How about soju?
Lay your sister down and come here.
I'll teach you how to eat and drink, the Korean way.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Eunchae.
If no guys come to you
because your face is full of injuries...
If they don't like you, and no one takes you,
then just come to me.
I'll live with you. Come to me.
I mean it. I'll take care of you.
What's wrong?
Water! Water!
What's wrong, Song Eunchae?
Oh, it's nothing. I'm all right.
[Pretty Minx]
Why aren't you picking it up?
It's Minju.
How do I look? Am I pretty?
You're pretty.
What do you think, Eunchae? Am I pretty?
Yes, you're beautiful.
Which earring goes with this outfit?
Diamond? Ruby? Sapphire?
Here.
It's better than bacon right?
It's because you have Korean taste buds.
Do you know my mother?
I do.
Does she live in this neighborhood? My mother?
No...
Why would a woman like her live in
a crappy neighborhood like this?
Truth will prevail in the end.
The ancient scholars were very brilliant
to create such words of wisdom.
My mother. Help me meet her.
I'll let you meet her. It's time for you to meet her.
Truth will prevail in the end.
The ancient scholars were brilliant. Right on.
You said this was better than bacon, so eat up!
I don't really like this necklace.
This necklace and this dress don't match, right?
They look good.
It's easy to tell when things are cheap.
Doesn't it devalue the dress?
That necklace wasn't cheap at all.
Yet not expensive. Only 1,000 dollars.
A thousand... That'd pay for
my family and me for a month.
Just wear it. You shine more brightly than any of that.
Really?
Let's get going, madam.
We're already running late.
Alright.
Are you a stalker?
Be quiet, brat!
Mom, Sukchae tried to hit me.
Why you little... Am I your friend?
You better not! Raise your arms!
No ones gets punished like this! I'm too old for it!
How old are you?
A 28-year-old with nothing better
to do than steal a guy's clothing?
Yeah!
If Yun's Mom finds out, we'll all
get kicked out of this house!
Yeah!
Yun is a star... A star!
And these, these are not Yun's.
These are considered Yun's fans' property.
How much is this? How much do you get exactly?
You want to buy it?
Each one is 30 dollars.
With a family discount I'll give
them to you for 150 dollars.
What the... They're 30 dollars each?
The handkerchief Yun used to wipe
his sweat at his concert
sold for 50 dollars.
50 dollars?
They put these in auctions. Items from stars.
Things used by Elvis Presley,
those are worth big money!
Unbelievable.
If we just go next door, there are
a million towels he wiped his sweat with.
I shouldn't wash any of them.
Exactly. So bring them to me.
So bring them and I'll let you in on the deal.
I'll give you ten percent.
How much would bowls and dishes sell for?
If we consider all the things he's used so far...
About 1,000 dollars.
Call the police, Minchae!
Tell them to take these two conspirators away.
Song Eunchae!
- Call them!
- Okay!
What are you doing?
I'm done with him.
Sooner than you expected, right?
You look sick.
What? You don't want me anymore?
You don't want me?
I'm sorry. For confusing you.
I'm making noodles. You want some?
Let's go.
Who is it?
Let me use the restroom.
Restroom. Let me use the restroom.
This isn't a public restroom.
I'm going to pee my pants.
Let me use it!
Pee yourself. No one's stopping you.
What a psycho!
Ahh!
[Episode 3 Preview]
I'm sorry. I'm flattered,
but I already have someone I like...
There's no room for you... I'm sorry!
Does that make any sense?
[A misunderstanding created love]
Hey.
Do you have a brother?
- No.
- Want to be mine?
Sure. I'll be your little bro.
[I didn't believe in love]
Minju and Yun can't swim!
How long did the doctor say I have to live?
I heard that I was dying.
Did you eat? It seems like you haven't.
Do you know anyone in Korea?